<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Football Club</string>

    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona FC</item>
        <item>Real Madrid FC</item>
        <item>Bayern Munchen FC</item>
        <item>Manchester City FC</item>
        <item>Manchester United FC</item>
        <item>Chelsea FC</item>
        <item>AC Milan FC</item>
        <item>Arsenal FC</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="club_desc">
        <item>Founded in 1899 by a group of Swiss, English and Catalan footballers led by Joan Gamper, the club has become a symbol of Catalan culture and Catalanism, hence the motto \'Mes que un club\' (\'More than a club\'). Unlike many other football clubs, the supporters own and operate Barcelona. It is the fourth-most valuable sports team in the world, worth $4.06 billion, and the world\'s second-richest football club in terms of revenue, with an annual turnover of €690.4 million.[2][3] The official Barcelona anthem is the \'Can not del Barca\', written by Jaume Picas and Josep Maria Espinas.[4]</item>
        <item>Real Madrid Club de Fútbol, sometimes known as just Real Madrid, is a Spanish football club from Madrid, Spain. It was started in 1902 and competes in La Liga (the Spanish top league). The \'Real\' in the club\'s name is Spanish for \'royal\', because it was blessed by the King of Spain in 1920.</item>
        <item>FC Bayern was founded in 1900 by 11 football players, led by Franz John.[5] Although Bayern won its first national championship in 1932,[6] the club was not selected for the Bundesliga at its inception in 1963.[7] The club had its period of greatest success in the middle of the 1970s when, under the captaincy of Franz Beckenbauer, it won the European Cup three times in a row (1974–1976)</item>
        <item>Manchester City Football Club is a football club based in Manchester, England, that competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football. Founded in 1880 as St. Mark\'s (West Gorton), it became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894. The club\'s home ground is the City of Manchester Stadium in east Manchester, to which it moved in 2003, having played at Maine Road since 1923.</item>
        <item>Manchester United Football Club, commonly known as Man United,[3][4] or simply United, is a professional football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England, that competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football. Nicknamed \'the Red Devils\', the club was founded as Newton Heath LYR Football Club in 1878, changed its name to Manchester United in 1902 and moved to its current stadium, Old Trafford, in 1910.</item>
        <item>Founded in 1905, the club\'s home ground since then has been Stamford Bridge.[7] Chelsea won its only First Division title in 1955, but saw limited success in various cup competitions until 2003, when the club was purchased by Russian billionaire Roman Abramovich.[8] Chelsea then saw heavy investment, and have since won eighteen honours under Abramovich.[9]</item>
        <item>Associazione Calcio Milan (Italian pronunciation: [assotʃatˈtsjoːne ˈkaltʃo ˈmiːlan]), commonly referred to as A.C. Milan or simply Milan, is a professional football club in Milan, Italy, founded in 1899.[5][6] The club has spent its entire history, with the exception of the 1980–81 and 1982–83 seasons, in the top flight of Italian football, known as Serie A since 1929–30.[5]</item>
        <item>Arsenal Football Club is a professional football club based in Islington, London, England, that plays in the Premier League, the top flight of English football. It has won 13 League titles, a record 13 FA Cups, two League Cups, the League Centenary Trophy, 15 FA Community Shields, one UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup and one Inter-Cities Fairs Cup.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/img_barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chelsea</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_arsenal</item>
    </array>

</resources>
